The Darkest Dawn is a action, science fiction film directed by Drew Casson.
Evacuated from their home, two teenage sisters unite with fellow survivors and escape
London by river to embark on an odyssey across the badlands of Britain.
Chloe Murdock, played by Bethan Mary Leadley.
Sam Murdoch, played by Cherry Wallis.
Bob, played by Stuart Ashen.
Cowen Rosewell, played by Drew Casson.
Hopper, played by Jamie Paul.
Ricky, played by Mawaan Rizwan.
King Push – Darkest Before Dawn: The Prelude is the second
studio album by American rapper Pusha T.
It was released on December 18, 2015, by GOOD Music and Def Jam Recordings.
The album was supported by three singles: "Untouchable", "M.F.T.R."
featuring The-Dream and "Crutches, Crosses, Caskets".
The album features guest appearances from The-Dream, Kanye West, ASAP Rocky, Ab-Liva, Beanie Sigel, Kehlani and Jill
Scott, with production handled by a variety of high-profile record producers, including Kanye West, J.
Cole, Timbaland, Q-Tip, Metro Boomin, Boi-1da, Hudson
Mohawke and Puff Daddy, among others.
The album serves as a prelude for his third solo album, Daytona
(originally titled King Push), which was released on May 25, 2018.
King Push – Darkest Before Dawn: The Prelude received widespread acclaim from critics,
who highly praised its unique lyricism and experimental production.
The tone is thought_provoking.